srchmgrd.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) of ironSource Ltd. (“ironSource”) describes the privacy practices with respect to the service (“Services,”). Please also review the End User License Agreement (“EULA”). ironSource operates certain software and browser extensions and add-ons that help you improve your browsing experience. 

1\. **_We Collect and Use_ **

1.1 _Basic Information_. We may collect technical information from your device. This information includes your type of browser(s), your IP address, your computer operating system details, andthe default homepage, start page, and new tab of your browser. We collect and use this information to enable the Services to work as it is intended, maintain, measure the performance of and improve the Services. We also collect your search query, but we will not use it for any purpose other than providing you with search results. 

1.2 _Information You Provide Us_. When you contact us, we keep a record of your communication with us (including your email address) to provide you with support services, and, if applicable, investigate any issues that you raise. We do not use this information for advertising purposes. 

1.3 _Cookies_. As part of the Software we may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information such as your usage data and to improve the Software. A cookie is a small text file saved on your computer to help store preferences and other information that is used on webpages that you visit. We may use cookies to better understand how you interact with the Software and to customize and improve the Software. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can change the settings of your browser at any time to delete/disable cookies. However, some features of the Software may not function properly if you disable cookies. 

1.4 _How we use your information_. We will use your information for the following purposes: 

1.4.1    Operating the Service – We use your information to the extent necessary to operate your service, and ensure compatibility with your device. 

1.4.2    Reporting – We use your information to generate reports. 

1.4.3    Search – We use your information to display you search results based on your search query, or send it to search companies as detailed below. 

1.4.4    Internal operations – We use your information to support our internal operations, including security, and internal debugging. 

1.4.5    Fraud detection and prevention – We use your information to detect and prevent fraud. 

1.4.6    Updates – We use your information in order to provide you with updates in connection with the Service. 

1.4.7    Offering you with additional software – We use your information to offer you with additional offers. 

1.5 _Provisions for European Users_. If you are located in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland, the following provisions apply to you: 

1.5.1    We act as a controller and process personal data as necessary for the performance of our contract with you (the EULA). 

1.5.2    Legal necessity - We may process your information for compliance with applicable legal obligations. 

1.5.3    Data subject rights - Please note that you have the right to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data we process as controllers, or to restrict or to object to processing of your personal data in accordance with the provisions of the GDPR. In order to submit a request for accessing and/or deleting your information, please send an email with your request to the following address: [support@searchmgr.com](mailto:support@searchmgr.com). Please note that we will process your request subject to verification of your identity. 

1.5.4    Complaint to supervisory authority - You also have the right to file a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority (e.g. of your country or domicile) where we have not addressed your concerns. 

1.6 _Data retention period_. We will store information collected from you as long as you are using our Services Once you delete our Services, please send an erasure request in accordance with the above procedure. 

2\. **_Information Sharing and Disclosure_ **

2.1. _General_. We do not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or in the event that we have a good faith belief that disclosure is permitted by law or is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with the law, a legal requirement or process, including without limitation, subpoenas, court orders, or other compulsory disclosures, or to establish, maintain or exercise our legal rights; (ii) enforce this Policy or the EULA; (iii) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or violation of third party rights; or (iv) protect our rights. In addition, in the event that we undergo a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be one of the assets sold or transferred. 

2.2. _Service Providers_. We currently use Amazon Web Services, Inc. and Google Cloud Platform servers to store your information. The Software may include Yahoo’s and/or Microsoft’s and/or Google’s search feed. You can read their privacy policies here: for Yahoo: <https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html> for Microsoft: [http://go.Microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=248686](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=248686) and got Google: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. 

2.3. _Corporate Affiliates_. We may also disclose your information to our corporate affiliates in order to help provide, understand, and improve the Services and our affiliates’ services, this means we may also internally combine information we have on you. 

2.4. _Provisions for European Users_. If you are located in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, and Switzerland, the following provisions apply to you: If you are located in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, we will transfer your information to the United States based on the Standard Contractual Clauses. If you wish to receive a copy of these clauses, please contact us through the below contact details. 

3\. **_Our Policy Towards Children_ **

The Services is not intended and/or directed to persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under that age has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information from our servers. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [support@searchmgr.com](mailto:support@searchmgr.com). 

4\. **_Changes to This Policy_ **. 

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make changes, that are significant in our sole discretion, in the way we treat your personal information, or to the Policy, we will provide you with notice as part of the Services or by any other means. Your continued use of the Services, following any change to this Policy, constitutes your complete and irrevocable acceptance of the updated Policy. If any changes to the Policy are not acceptable to you, you may uninstall the Services. 

5\. **_Contact Information_ **

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at [support@searchmgr.com](mailto:support@searchmgr.com).
